uh hey guys uh welcome to the next video so in this video we will see the supply chain attacks
so in 2021 there is a service called Solarwin like Kasia so in this uh they compromised
the Kasia and a lot and a lot of uh company were involved uh there are next poiter uh
and a uh put a ransomware uh by using this Kasia supply chain attack so let me see uh supply
chain attack so it's a 2021 so the threat attack are used probably the rebel ransomware
uh used the Kasia so we used to spread their ransomware across the uh customers okay so
i will give us certain few examples of uh supply chain attack let me go for a binder website
so if you compromise this binder website and if you put if you put your malicious executable
instead of the uh original binder app so if i click on this uh download button so my
binder is going to uh download so if you have if you can able to uh yep if you can able to compromise this
uh download vintraar um button or the vintraar server so the server will be hosting the exe
right uh the vintraar.exe right so if you can able to compromise that so that time
the customers will uh probably the customers will download the vintraar so not only one
customers so many customers uh will download the vintraar and they will executing the vintraar
in their machine okay so whenever they are executing they will be you'll be getting a reverse
connection so because you are putting the malware instead of the original vintraar right
so this is called as the uh supply chain attack okay so there's one tool uh like uh
called as a CC cleaner ID I think uh that has been compromised for uh uh supply chain attack
so the protector is the same scenario like uh what like how I explained in the vintraar
so this CC cleaner is uh uh computer's cleaning up tool it will be cleaning the
term directory it will be cleaning some uh term files and all uh so the detectors uh instead of
CC cleaner the protector installed uh the malicious exe on the CC cleaner and they can
they can able to easily compromise all the customers who is downloading uh the CC cleaner okay
so uh the other way if you can able to inject some code inside the vintraar.exe
malicious code inside the vintraar.exe so that time also you'll be getting the reverse connection
from the uh installed uh from the installed uh computer slide so who is downloading the malicious
vintraar so you will be getting a reverse connection from all the machines okay so this is how
the supply chain attacks will work if you need to refer the supply chain attack more
so my best suggestion will be uh because he has supply chain attack
so this one of the service so the protector compromised this and uh he can inject a malicious
code inside it and he can get uh uh uh a reverse connection from that okay uh so another part
if you can able to compromise the Microsoft Windows uh update related database
that time also if you have a capability to put your uh malware inside the database
uh so that time uh all the Microsoft users Windows users so they will be getting an uh
Windows update so the malware will be automatically installed on the uh update or machines
and you will be getting a uh a reverse connections uh from that okay so let's
this is the scenario of a supply chain attack let's scope of this video and we will continue our
discussion in the next video you guys bye bye